itsupportguides.com 2018-07-30

# Privacy policy – IT Support Guides

We recognize that the privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit this website.

## Information logged

When visiting this website, a record of your visit is logged. Data is recorded for statistical purposes only and is used to help improve this website. This may include, but not be limited to, the following information as supplied by your browser (eg: Internet Explorer):

  * your server address
  * your operating system (for example Windows, MAC etc)
  * your top level domain name (for example .com, .gov, .au, .uk etc)
  * the date and time of the visit to the site
  * the pages accessed and the documents downloaded
  * the previous site visited, and
  * your type of browser used.

No attempt will be made to identify users or their browsing activities except in the unlikely event of an investigation, where a law enforcement agency (or other government agency) exercises a legal authority to inspect Internet Service Provider (ISP) logs (eg. by warrant, subpoena or notice to produce).

## Cookies

A cookie is a small file that is sent to your web browser from a web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies can make websites easier to use by storing information about your preferences on a particular website. This information remains on your computer after you close your browser.

This website uses cookies only for the purpose of enabling the web services offered by this website, such as saving your personal preferences.

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings.  However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our website as well as other websites.

## Advertising

Third-party advertisements are used on this website.

Advertisers may use cookies to serve ads based on your prior visits to this website.

Google’s use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads based on your visit to this websites and/or other websites.

You can opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting [Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/ads/preferences/).

## Links to other sites

This site contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the content or the privacy practices of other websites and we encourage you to examine each website’s privacy policy.

Please note:  
This personal information protection statement does not extend beyond this website. When linking to other websites from any of our websites, we recommend that you read the relevant privacy statement of that website to familiarise yourself with the privacy policy that applies to it.
